

Date of birth: September 5, 1984 Language: Persian (Native), English Grade: Male

Marital Status: Married Country of citizenship: Iran Phone (+98-28) 33686323

Mobile: (+98) 9122819015 (WhatsApp)

E-mail:

MJ.Namazifar@gmail.com MJ.Namazifar@yahoo.com Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/mj-namazifar

Skype live: @mj.namazifar

♣: https://namazifar.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Hackerrank.com Codewars.com Stackoverflow.com

Mohammad Javad Namazifar

Objective

I'm interested in computer science, software engineering, artificial intelligence and robotics. With +9 year experience as .NET developer using C#, Experienced with relational database in Microsoft SQL Server database, design & T-SQL. debugging and problem-solving in order to provide proper solutions. I am very interested in sharing my expertise and motivation with your developing team. A few of my obvious features that can be useful in advancing your organizational goals are the spirit of teamwork and my problem-solving ability. I am interested in working in an environment where my expectations are far more than my level of knowledge and skill, and this is a serious stimulus for my personal growth.

Work Experience

1- Nafis Nakh, Full Stack [Feb2022–Present]

URL: https://NafisNakh.com/

Nafis Nakh Company has been operational since 2003 and it aims to produce various filament polyester yarns and to keep up with large market demand. During my stay in this company, I am working the following fields:

- NafisERP ASP.NET MVC and Database MSSQL Server
- NafisWebService ASP.NET MVC and Database MSSQL Server

2- BIG¹, IT-Designer and developer [Aug 2020 – Feb2022]

URL: http://www.Polfilm.net/

POLFILM is the first and largest leading manufacturer of BOPP films in Iran. I am currently working as a senior software engineer in the IT department of Bayazian Industrial Group. During my stay in this company, I designed and implemented the following fields:

- Sales and Marketing ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server
- Production Planning Control (PPC) Plate, Polfilm, Petco and Atlasfilm company, C# WinForms and Database MSSQL Server
- Implemented Processes and Services provided by the IT department in the software platform (ITIL²) at Plate, Polfilm, Petco, Atlasfilm, Atlas Boobin and PayKaran company.
- Designed a Dbsyncer Synchronize distributed databases to integrate data into a single database based on scheduler, C# WCF and Database MSSQL Server
- Implemented REST APIs with ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server, for the provide services to other enterprise applications, based JWT token-based authentication
- Analyze and integrate multiple heterogeneous data sources across the company using MS SOL Server, SSIS
- AzureDevops and Scrum process Implementer

¹ Baiazian Industrial Group

² Information Technology Infrastructure Library

Achievement:

· Web development, ITIL, WCF, good knowledge of Integrate and Db syncing

Learning:

• REST APIs, SSIS, AzureDevops, Scrum Process

Tech stack: WCF/MSSQL/ SSIS

3- Arta Company, Senior Software Engineer [Jun 2019 - Sep 2020]

TAMASHACHI website belongs to Arta company. The company informs users about the news and results of live sports such as football. I worked part-time in Arta company for more than a year, during my stay in this company, I designed and implemented the following fields:

- Implemented REST APIs with ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server, Back-end Website Online results of football sports events, https://tamashachi.com
- API Football Analysis
- Designing a database for football data, teams, players, events and etc.
- Implementing a Back-end synchronize database with Football data server
- Serving in Persian and English language to the website and mobile App
- Implementing a dashboard to test the services provided, based on swagger

Achievement:

• experience a real team work, Commitment to work and deadlines

Learning:

· Walk through real development ASP.Net Core

Tech stack: ASP.Net Core/ MSSQL / JSON/

4- SDC¹, IT-Designer and developer [Jul 2013 - Aug 2020]

URL: http://www.seven-diamonds.com

I worked for more than 7 years in the IT department of Seven Diamonds Industrial company which is in the field of steel industry, during this time, I worked on the following fields:

- Management Information System(MIS), C# and Database Programming
- Microsoft Dynamics AX (ERP)
 - o Installing and configuring of the Dynamics AX 2012 R2/R3 ERP
 - Workflow configuration and setup
 - o Users and Role management
 - o Procurement and sourcing
 - O Product and Procurement Catalog / Policy Rules
 - o Procedures and processes of Procurement, Quality Control, Warehouse
 - o Product and Service information management
 - Procedures and Production Control Processes

• Design and implementation of Processes and Services provided by the IT department in the software platform (ITIL)

- User Panel for End user to track and report problems
- Incident Management
- o Service/Incident Catalog
- Business Rules (organize all the incoming requests and perform actions such as delivering them to IT groups)
- Automatic Request Distribution
- Service Level Agreement (SLA)
- Asset Management
- User Survey
- Content management system, SharePoint 2016
- Design and implementation of Stop monitoring software related production lines

_

¹ Seven Diamonds Company – Steel Alborz Company

- Lessening and receiving information about stop-of-production lines from control boards in the parallel port
- Insert information about the stops and start-up of production lines in the database
- O Data mining and reporting on duration time stop the production lines
- Implementation of software amortized costs of company units on production lines, to calculate the cost of goods
 - o Receive information on costs of production and non-production centers
 - The formation of a multiplex table, based on the financial and industrial accounting period
 - Calculated and amortized the costs to the manufacturing centers

• Seven-Diamonds Company Website

- Design concepts and contents according to functional requirement company
- Implement responsive multilingual WordPress website mock-up into fully functioning websites employing HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jOuery and Bootstrap

• Quality defect detection Steel Products Seven Diamonds Industry using Machine Learning and Image Processing

- Collecting images of product quality defects
- Classification of product's quality defects by *OpenCV* and machine learning algorithms

Achievement:

• Getting good knowledge of development in ERP

Learning:

 MS Dynamics AX 2012, ITIL, WordPress, Walk through real development in .Net and C#, Stored Procedures

Tech stack: MS Dynamics AX | MSSQL | Deep Learning|

Research Experience

1- MRL¹, MRL, @Home Robot Team [JUL 2012 – JAN 2014]

I was with MRL @home team at Azad University of Qazvin, Department of Electronics, Computer and Information Technology Engineering From 2012 to 2014 as a researcher with interests in

- Human-Robot Interaction (HRI)
- Target Tracking
- Human-Following Mobile Robot
- Laser and Vision-based Tracking Multiple Moving Targets with a Mobile Robot
- Sensor and Classifier Fusion for Fast Human Detection
- Detection of Human Pairs of Legs using a 2D Laser Range Finder(LRF)

2- AUT², Algorithm and Computational Geometry Laboratory [DEC 2011 – FEB 2013]

I was with Algorithm and Computational Geometry Laboratory Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran, Department of Computer From 2011 to 2013 as a researcher with interests in

- Watchman Route Problem (WRP)
- Freeze Tag Problem (FTP)
- Swarm Robotic
- Heuristic and Meta-Heuristic Algorithm

3- MRL³, Rescue Robot Team [DEC 2007 – JAN 2012]

I was a member of Rescue robot RoboCup team at Azad University of Qazvin, Department of Electronics, Computer and Information Technology Engineering From 2007 to 2012 during which I have experienced in these fields:

- Customize kernel Linux OS for Embedded PC
- Developing an embedded Linux operating system for robots
- Autonomous robot exploration in unknown environments
- Victim Detection
- Merge 2d laser Map
- Sensors Robot Stabilizing with PID controller

¹ Mechatronics Research Laboratory, Azad University of Qazvin, Iran

² Amirkabir University Tehran, Department of Computer and Information Technology Engineering

³ Mechatronics Research Laboratory, Azad University of Qazvin, Iran

Teaching Experience

Instructor at Islamic Azad University Qazvin, Department of Computer & IT Engineering [2012–2014]

Course: Operating System, Computer Workshop

Education

- M.Sc. in Computer Engineering (Software) Electronics, Computer and IT Engineering Department, Islamic Azad University, Qazvin Branch, Iran [Fall 2010 – 2013]
 - o Thesis: Presenting Algorithms for Waking up a Swarm of Robots with Radial approach
 - O Supervisor: Dr.Alireza Bagheri and Dr.Keivan Borna
- B.Sc. in Computer Engineering (Software) *Electronics, Computer and IT Engineering Department*, Islamic Azad University, Oazvin Branch, Iran [Fall 2006 – 2009]
 - o Project: Multiplayer game and chat in Mobile device based on the Bluetooth
 - Supervisor: Dr.Behrouz Masoumi

Membership and Professional Experience

- Member of *Talent in Understanding Young Researchers and elite Club*, Islamic Azad University, Iran [2008 Present]
 Link: My page in BPJ
- Member of Technical Committee (TC), International Iran Open RoboCup Competition, Tehran, Iran - @Home League [2013 – 2013]
- Member of Technical Committee (TC), *International Iran Open RoboCup Competition*, *Tehran*, *Iran* Rescue Real League [2015 2015]

Interests and activities

• ERP, ITIL, Integrate multiple heterogeneous data sources, Web Developing

Patents and publications

- 1- F. Barazandeh, M. Norouzi, M. Yaghobi, M. Moshfeghi, M.J.Namazifar, M. Ghaffari Jadidi, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, J.Chegini,J.Zolghadr, M.Rahmani, M.R.Siboni, M.Namazifar, M.Jadaliha, S.M. Mavaei, B. Asadi, M. Farahbakhsh "RoboCupRescue 2008 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2008
- 2- A.M.Shahri, M.Norouzi, M.Yaghobi, S.M.Mavaei, M.J.Namazifar, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, J.Chegini, M.Rahmani, M.Namazifar, B.Asadi "RoboCupRescue 2009 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2009
- 3- A.M.Shahri, J.Chegini, **M.J.Namazifar**, H.montazerzohur, B.MehdiKhani, M.karimi, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, V.Azizi "RoboCupRescue 2010 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2010
- 4- A.M.Shahri, J.Chegini, **M.J.Namazifar**, B.MehdiKhani, E.Saeidi, M.Salehzadeh, A.R.HajMohammadhosseini, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, M.Rahmani, M.E.Mashat, V.Azizi "RoboCupRescue 2011 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2011
- 5- F.Mahmoudi, V.Mokhtari Hassanabad, F.Maroofkhani, **MJ.Namazifar**, AA.Pasdar, A.Hosseini, F.Abdollahi, F.Abazari, N.Nabavi, MR.Kakvand and A.Shabani Asl. "*RoboCup @Home 2012 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description*", 2012
- 6- F.Mahmoudi, R.Fathzadeh, A.Hosseini, **M.J.Namazifar**, N.Nabavi, F.Abdollahi, M.Iranikhah, S.Bayani, F.Abazari, R.shahabian and H.Bagher "*RoboCup @Home 2013 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description*", 2013
- 7- MJ.Namazifar, ar.Bagheri, k.Borna"An approximation algorithm for the awakening of robots in Euclidean space" National Conference on Science, Engineering, New Ideas (8), Tonekabon, Branch future institutions of higher learning. 2014 (in Persian)
- 8- **MJ.Namazifar**, A.Bagheri, K.Borna, "Linear time constant factor approximation algorithm for the Euclidean `Freeze-Tag` robot ", Advances in Computer Science: an International Journal, 2015.

Certificates & Awards received

- Presenting a plan entitled "Create Intelligent Autonomy in Rescue Mobile Robot", Fajr International Invention & Innovations Exhibition (FINEX 2008), Tehran, Iran. [February 2008].
- Being exempted from master's program entrance examination as an "Exceptional Talented" student in Qazvin Islamic Azad University, 2009.
- **Scholarship** of Azad University, Qazvin Branch [2006-2013].

- Certification training course "Principles of Supervision" Qazvin University Jahad, 2016.
- Certification training course "Process Management and Modeling Process with BPMN Focus", 2017.

• @Home Robot League:

- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup @Home in Iran, 2012.
- 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup @Home in Iran, 2013.

• Rescue Real Robot League:

- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, **Turkey** 2011.
- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **Best Autonomy** Challenge, **Turkey** 2011.
- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **Manipulation Challenge**, **Turkey** 2011.
- 3rd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, **Austria** 2009.
- Best Autonomy Robot in International Thailand Rescue Robot Competition, 2008.
- o 3rd Place in **Thailand** Rescue Robot Competition, 2008.
- o 1st Place in **Khwarizmi** Robotic competition, Iran 2008.
- 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, China 2008.
- o 3rd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **League Locomotion Challenge** (*Best in Class Mobility*), **China** 2008.
- Award of Technical Challenge in **Best Mapping Algorithm** at International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real, 2008.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2008.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2009.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2010.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2011.

Projects

• Qt Cross Compile for beagle Bone Black, Micro Alborz System Company [July 2015]

Setting up and configuration Qt and toolchain for cross-compiling

- Cross-Compiling Qt for Beagle board ARM based targets and board bring up using Angstrom/Debian Linux
- o Setting up remote Debugging embedded software based on Qtcreator
- Setting up Linux Device Driver Serial RS232/486

Skills

Programming

- C/C++, JAVA, Python in Linux and Windows
- C#, Pascal, Delphi, Visual Basic, Borland C++, Visual C++, x86 Assembly, Prolog
- Shell Programming in Linux and Windows
- Web Programming ASP .NET Core MVC, HTML, JavaScript, Css, XML, JSON, Caml Technique
- SQL and NoSQL database
- WordPress, SharePoint, SharePoint Designer, InfoPath Designer
- Java Mobile Programming
- Low level Programming, Network Programming
 - o Socket Programming TCP/UDP and RTSP / RTP
 - Implementing CRC
 - Implementing XML based communication protocol

Packages/Libraries

- Qt Programming in Windows and Linux
- J2me Programming for Cell Phone
- Familiar with OpenGL programming
- Graphics Programming with OpenGL, GlScene
- Cross-Compiler Toolchain
- OpenCV / Deep Learning

Data Bases

• MS SQL Server, MS Access, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Robotics Packages

• ROS (Robot Operating System)

Hardware Integration/Programming

 Hokuyo Laser Range Finders (LRF), XSens MTi, Embedded Industrial IBM Compatible, Pan-tilt CMUcam, Beagle Bone Board (BBB), Dynamixel RX-64

Operating Systems

- MS Dos, Windows (Most Versions), Linux (Fedora, OpenSUSE, Ubuntu, Tiny OS, SliTaz)
- Customize Kernel Linux, Embedded Linux Developing

ERP

Microsoft Dynamics AX 2009, 2012 R2, 2012 R3

Project Management

- SVN, Git in Linux and Windows
- Agile/Scrum

References

Hossein Nazari: h.nazari@seven-diamonds.com

Dr. Alireza M.Shahri: shahri@iust.ac.ir
Dr. Mohammad Norouzi: mh.norouzi@gmail.com

Hobbies

Soccer, Music, Sudoku, Watching documentary

Graduate Courses

I had some studies on graduate courses such as

- Advanced Operating System and Distributed Operating System
- Advanced Database and Distributed Database
- Parallel Processing Algorithms
- **Advance Computer Graphics**
- Computational Geometry
- Multi Agent Systems
- Data Compression

Last updated: June 7, 2022